http://www.british-antiqueclocks.com/privacy/

P.A. Oxley Menu
P.A. Oxley
Vintage WatchesStock ListLongcase ClocksAutomata Longcase ClocksBrass Dial Longcase ClocksEnglish Longcase ClocksGrandfather ClocksLacquered/Chinoiserie Longcase ClocksLondon Longcase ClocksMahogany Longcase ClocksMarquetry Longcase ClocksMoonphase Longcase ClocksOak Longcase ClocksPainted Dial Longcase ClocksQuarter Striking Longcase ClocksRegulator Longcase ClocksScottish Longcase ClocksWalnut Longcase ClocksBarometersWheel BarometersStick BarometersBracket/Table & Wall ClocksBracket ClocksMantel ClocksWall ClocksContact
British Antique Clocks Privacy Policy
1. Our beliefs regarding data protection and user privacy
Data Protection is a right all users must have
We have a duty of care to people using our website
2. Relevant privacy policy legislation
Our business and website conforms to the following data protection legislation:
UK Data Protection Act 1988 (DPA)
EU Data Protection Directive 1995 (DPD)
EU General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR)
3. Information this website collects and why we collect it
This website collects and uses personal information for the following reasons:
3.1 Site usage tracking
Like most websites, we use Google Analytics to track user interaction. We use this data to determine the number of people using our site, to better understand how they find & use our web pages and to see their journey through the website.
Although Google Analytics records data such as your geographical location, device, internet browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. Google Analytics also records your computer’s IP address which could be used to personally identify you but Google do not grant us access to this.
3.3 Contact forms
Unless you explicitly consent to get news and updates via email from us, we will never store your details on our website.
The data entered into any forms on this site is collated into an email and sent to us over the Simple Mail Transfer Protocol. Our servers are protected by TLS (sometimes known as SSL) meaning that the email content is encrypted using SHA-2, 256-bit cryptography before being sent.
3.4 Newsletter
If you choose to join our email newsletter, you'll receive updates every so often regarding our opening times and if you have a website or email with us, we'll provide you updates on any downtime and server maintenance work to be carried out.
To subscribe or unsubscribe from our newsletter, please use the link below:
http://www.british-antiqueclocks.com/newsletter/manage/
If you are under 16 years old, you must obtain parental consent before subscribing to our newsletter
4. How we store your information
All data held by British Antique Clocks is secure. Firewalls block all public access to our systems with the exception of secure browser (https), email and mobile network connections necessary to provide our services.
Key employees have access to our systems with multi-layer security in order to provide essential maintenance and development activity.
5. About this website's server
This website is hosted on a dedicated server supplied by 1&1 Ltd within a secure data centre located in Munich, Germany.
All traffic (transferal of files) between this website and your browser is encrypted and delivered over HTTPS.
6. Third Party Data Processors
These third parties have been carefully chosen and all of them comply with the GDPR legislation set out in section 2.0. All third parties are EU-U.S Privacy Shield compliant.
Google (Privacy policy)
Flaydemouse Media Ltd (Our site developers and host)
7. Data Breaches
We will report any unlawful data breach of this website’s database or the database(s) of any of our third party data processors to any and all relevant persons and authorities within 72 hours of the breach if it is apparent that personal data stored in an identifiable manner has been stolen.
8. Data Controller
The data controller of this website is:
P.A. Oxley, The Old Rectory, Cherhill Calne, Wiltshire, SN11 8UX
Whose registered and operating office is:
P. A. OxleyThe Old RectoryCherhill CalneWiltshireSN11 8UX
9. Changes to privacy policy
This privacy policy may change from time to time inline with legislation or industry developments. We will not explicitly inform our clients or website users of these changes. Instead, we recommend that you check this page occasionally for any policy changes.
10. Cookie policy
Cookies are small text files that websites save to your device & often include a randomly generated ID. Some cookies are automatically deleted after you finish using the website.
We use Google Analytics, a popular web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to help us to analyse how users use the site. It counts the number of visitors and tells us things about their behaviour overall – such as the typical length of stay on the site or the average number of pages a user views.
Learn more about Google Analytics and it’s use of cookies
11. Opt-out
In order to provide website visitors with more choice on how data is collected by Google Analytics, Google has developed the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to stop data being sent to Google Analytics. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on does not affect usage of the website in any other way. A link to further information on the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is provided below for your convenience.
Google Analytics opt-out
For more information on the usage of cookies by Google Analytics please see the Google website. A link to the privacy advice for this product is provided below for your convenience.
Google Analytics Privacy Policy
12. Disabling cookies
If you would like to restrict the use of cookies you can control this in your Internet browser. Links to advise on how to do this for the most popular Internet browsers are provided below for convenience and will be available for the Internet browser of your choice either online or via the software help (normally available via key F1).
For further help on removing / blocking cookies, please see the following links:
Google Chrome
Mozilla Firefox
Apple Safari
Microsoft Edge
